

SUBASH GONGWA

Graphic Designer

Able to create effective and innovative designs to convey desired idea. Experience working with clients to identify needs and present solutions. Collaborating with marketing, sales, and product development departments. Flexible problemsolver able to adapt to changing circumstances and needs

Contact

+977-9840564096

subashgongwanepal@gmail.com

Ohapasi, Kathmandu

Education

(Under Graduate (Bachelor)) - BBS 2nd year

Public Youth Campus Tribhuvan University Paknajol, Kthmandu

+2 HSEB

Navodit Vidhya Kunja HSEB Samakoshi, Kathmandu

Skills

Organized

Communication

Teamwork

Meeting deadlines

Critical thinking

Experience

Graphic Designer

DIGITAL PRINT NEPAL

Oct 2022 - Aug 2024

Creation of customized designs for ID cards, lanyards, banners, and various sublimation printing materials. With a blend of creativity and technical expertise, I ensure each product meets high-quality standards and reflects the unique identity and vision of our clients.

Graphic Designer

Xcelerate Consulting Balkhu

Dec 2021 - Sept 2022

Creation of visual designs for different products for Amazon listing image and A+ content.Conceptualize designs, prepare mockups, and create the designs.

Graphic Designer

Maxwell Impex

Jan 2019 - Aug 2022

Creation of visual designs for printing such as brochures, labels, business cards, and a range of other marketing materials. Conceptualize designs, prepare mockups, and create the final designs for printing. Ensure that the dimensions and technical specifications are suitable for printing.

Junior Graphic Designer

Friends Art

Feb 2018 - Dec 2018

As a junior, I assist graphic designers in creating customized designs for banners, stamps, stickers, menu cards, ID cards, and other sublimation printing materials.